I'm going to watch their thing but because you
voy a ver lo de ellos pero porque me
're giving me so much there are many to see it
estáis dando mucho muchos hay para verlo
okay And I Juan has an opinion on what he considers
vale Y yo Juan opina de lo que considera
an exaggerated ego fight you say that
una lucha de egos exagerada dices que
everyone lives better than most
todo viven mejor que la mayoría de las
people but ambition puts it in the
personas pero la ambición ponte en el
recognition for more people than their
reconocimiento por más personas que su
own audience and defends Ibai's award
propia audiencia y defiende el premio de
saying that he deserved it let's watch the
ibai diciendo que él lo merecía a ver
first part I don't know I don't know I don't know what
primera parte No sé no sé no sé a qué
this exaggerated ego fight is about
viene esta lucha de egos tan exagerada
these shitty fights and this [ __ ]
estas peleas de [__] y estas [__]
nonsense when it's that I don't know I don't know what more we want the truth is like we live off what we like we earn a [ __ ] lot of money we're surrounded at least I speak for myself personally by incredible people what more do you want I mean we're in a better situation than 95
estamos en una mejor situación que el 95
99.9% of the people our age man in
99,9% de la peña de nuestra edad tío en
a better situation at all [ __ ]
una mejor situación a todos los [__]
levels at all I
niveles a todos
understand that we always want something more
entiendo que siempre queremos algo más
human beings always it's not that you no matter how
los seres humanos siempre no es que tú
much your
por mucho que tú estés cubierto de las
basic needs are covered you always want something
necesidades básicas siempre quieres algo
more there's always something that you're missing
más siempre hay algo que te falta
always always always I only understand why
siempre siempre siempre yo solo entiendo
of course I understand and we're
yo por supuestísimo que lo entiendo y a
all excited to win an
todo el mundo nos hace ilusión ganar un
award of course and we're all
premio por supuestísimo y a todo el
excited to have
mundo nos hace ilusión tener
recognition but the esland
reconocimiento pero es que los esland no
is not recognition from the people who
es reconocimiento de la gente que a ti
see you the people who see you are already
te ve la gente que a ti te ve ya te está
giving you recognition every [ __ ]
dando reconocimiento a todos los [__]
day and they were sending you messages on
días y te estaban dando mensajes por
all the social networks and such the
todas las redes sociales y tal los
Airlines are recognitions from people
Airlines son reconocimientos de la gente
who don't see you too and the people who don't see you
que a ti no te ve también y la gente que
should help you out
a ti no te ve te debería ayudar la [__]
like I don't give a damn the people who don't see me
como a mí me la suda a mí la gente que
okay the people in
que no me ve vale la gente de la
Pepito's community make my [ __ ]
comunidad de Pepito me sube el [__]
ass rise when they think that I'm not I don't care you
cipotes que piensen que yo no soy es que
give it to me you still understand me
me da igual me dais Igual me entendéis
because you don't see me [ __ ] I haven't seen
porque no me veis [__] No he visto ni
a minute man [ __ ] [ __ ] exactly like
un minuto tío [__] [__] tal cual por
finally one of these greats who tells something like that
fin uno de estos grandes que cuenta algo
man who speaks it like that man So my
así tío que lo habla así tío Entonces mi
opinion doesn't matter to me he understands me and I can't care it
opinión no me importa me entiende y no
's that I can't
me puede importar es que no me puede
care less if you don't see me It's normal
importar menos si no me ves Es normal
that you think that I don't deserve it if you do
que pienses que yo no me merezco si es
n't see me what the [ __ ] are you going to  give your opinion but it's
que no me ves qué [__] vas a opinar pero
normal it's normal it's the most
es que es normal es normal es lo más
normal thing in the world So you can't
normal del mundo Entonces no te puedes
expect everyone to dance to your
esperar que todo el mundo te baile el
tune you can't expect it you know it can't
agua no te lo puedes esperar sabes no
the people
puede te va a bailar el agua la gente
who see you and the people who
que a ti te ve y la gente que a ti te
appreciate you and the people who consume what you
aprecia y la gente que consume lo que tú
do are going to dance to your tune yes it is instead of making a
haces si lo es la en vez de hacer un
video of Greg would have organized it Auro
vídeo de Greg lo hubiera organizado Auro
wins auron Those are the people who are
gana auron Esa es la gente que a ti te
going to dance to your tune because the people
va a bailar el agua porque la gente a la
who the people who appreciate you the rest I mean yes it
que la gente que te aprecia el resto O
would be cool Yes he would be
sea pues sí vale estaría Guay Sí estaría
cool such but not me what do I know man what do I
guapo tal pero que tampoco yo que sé tío
know I'm the first one who would
yo que sé yo soy el primero que se
have been motivated if I had won but I
habría motivo si hubiera ganado pero yo
was so clear so Clear because I know
tenía tan claro tan Claro porque sé
where I am or do you think that I don't know
dónde estoy o creéis que no sé
perfectly well who I am I know perfectly well
perfectamente quién soy sé perfectamente
where I am I know perfectly well What
dónde estoy sé perfectamente Cuáles son
my chances are I know perfectly well who I am
mis posibilidades sé perfectamente quién
Within this world I know
soy Dentro de este mundillo lo sé
perfectly well and 6 100% that I can't
perfectamente y 6 al 100% que yo no
win that then I go
puedo ganar eso entonces yo voy
calmly you know I go very calmly
tranquilo sabes yo voy muy tranquilo
but of course I turn around and I have my 14
pero claro yo me giro y tengo mis 14
childhood friends sitting then I
colegas de la infancia sentado entonces
say I get on the dick you understand That's it
digo me subo al nabo me entiendes Eso es
that I won So I
lo que yo he ganado Entonces yo me di la
turned around and when they say that the one who
vuelta y cuando dicen que el que ha
won and I say dude it's normal it's normal it's that
ganado y digo illo es que es normal es
Who's going to win if
que es normal es que Quién va a ganar si
not While you're there no one else is going to win
no Mientras estéis ahí no va a ganar
if you keep doing things like that I
otro si sigue haciendo las cosas así me
mean Well there either I don't
refiero Bueno ahí tampoco Ahí tampoco
agree there either eh while he was leaving
estoy de acuerdo eh mientras que se iba
and no one else is going to win it's that the
y tampoco va a ganar otro es que el
streamer of the year is that that is very
streamer del año es que eso es muy
relative the streamer of the year the best
relativo el streamer del año el mejor
streamer is that they are very relative It's that I
streamer es que son muy relativos Es que
think that it depends on who
yo creo que eso depende de quién
organizes the event another person is not going to win it's not going to
organice el evento no va a ganar otra
happen it's not going to happen
persona no va a ocurrir no va a pasar
get it out of your head no but you
quítatelo de la cabeza no pero tú te lo
deserve it thank you thank you but no no
mereces que gracias gracias pero que no
the year especially this year put
que no el año sobre todo este año ponte
in 2023 fishing was the one who paid the
en 2023 pesca fue el que le pagó el
trip for all of yo Juan's friends and
viaje a todos los amigos de yo Juan y
why Karime What was the promo I haven't
por qué Karime Cuál fue la promo no he
seen that promo is it true in the end I didn't
visto esa promo es verdad al final no me
find out Why was the promo it was a
enteré de Por qué fue la promo fue una
story and that's it a promo it was and that's it he
historia y ya está una promo fue y ya
paid the trip for 15 people if he
está le pagó el viaje a 15 personas si
doesn't win and wow then who the hell is going to
no gana y vaya entonces quién [__] va a
win who  [ __ ] is going to win says
ganar quién pollas va a ganar dice ponte
think about it you have very top events there every year
a pensar tienes ahí cada año eventos muy
But well auron has also done
top Pero bueno auron ha hecho también
some very nice events [ __ ] the [ __ ]
unos eventos Muy guapos [__] lo del
squid game thing is an
[__] juego del calamar es una Sacada
incredible Sacada Can you explain it to me
increíble Me lo puedes explicar
simply by putting together the evening 2 The
simplemente por montar la velada 2 La
promo was to wear Pull and Bear clothes to the
promo fue ir con ropa Pull and Bear al
event and that's it but that's not cool Well yes they
evento y ya pero eso no fresca Bueno sí
are inditex groups for that [ __ ] madness
son grupos inditex por esa [__] locura
that I know they shouldn't win an award
que sé que no debería ganar un premio
for one thing but for many no but of
por una cosa sino por muchas no pero
course it hasn't been one it has been many and
claro no ha sido una han sido muchas y
what it represents not for the community and
lo que representa no para la comunidad y
all the roll that I understand that you
todo el rollo que yo entiendo que tú
then say Look I see it and I get
luego digas vos Mira yo lo veo y me
bored okay there are people who say I watch
aburro vale hay gente que dice yo me veo
your live and I get bored perfect I
tu directo y me aburro perfecto yo me
watch the auronplay live shows I get bored I
veo los directos auronplay me aburro yo
don't watch mariani's live shows I get bored
no veo los directos de mariani me aburro
and I'm normal bro normal nobody is
y yo normal hermano normal nadie te está
asking you to agree with
pidiendo que estés de acuerdo con otras
65 million other people nobody is
65 millones de personas nadie te lo está
asking you that's what this is about
pidiendo de eso va esto de opiniones
different opinions completely free and everything
distintas completamente gratis y todo
how is it possible that this influencer has
cómo es posible que esta influencer haya
taken 13 people to Mexico
llevado a 13 personas a México
completely free and everything paid for  for
completamente gratis y todo pagado por
a brand the streamer and I Juan who for
una marca el streamer y yo Juan que para
many of them The streamer of the year of
muchos de ellos El streamer del año de
the awards is Lan took his 13 friends
los premios es Lan llevó a sus 13 amigos
completely free to Mexico thanks to
completamente gratis a México gracias a
the Spanish brand that told him Hey I'll
la marca española que le dijo Oye yo te
pay you hotel accommodation everything
pago hotel alojamiento todo lo que
you want the only thing you have to do is
quieras lo único que tienes que hacer es
upload a photo which if we
subir una foto lo cual si nos ponemos a
think about it is a
pensar es una acción por una foto
quite profitable action for the brand because
bastante rentable para la marca porque
the awards in their golden minute reached
los premios en su minuto de oro llegaron
1.8 million viewers And if we
a 1.8 millones de espectadores Y si
consider that according to official figures the
consideramos que según cifras oficiales
content creators of more than 7
a los creadores de contenido de más de 7
million followers on Instagram were
millones de seguidores en instagram se
paid in 2016 150 thousand dollars we
les pagaba en 2016 150 mil dólares
would be talking about that they Juan
estaríamos hablando que ellos Juan le
would have paid him 20 thousand dollars not to
hubieran pagado 20 mil dólares eso sin
mention the most important thing which is to
mencionar lo más importante que es
indirectly turn him into a
convertirlo indirectamente en embajador
brand ambassador because the personality of the
de marca porque la personalidad del
streamer represents what pulan ver
streamer representa lo que pulan ver
wants to communicate as brand values and
quiere comunicar como valores de marca y
above all that empathizes with his audience in
sobre todo que empatiza con su audiencia
other words when the kids see
otras palabras cuando los chiquillos ven
a celebrity they admire
una celebridad a la que admiran
automatically they want to look like her
automáticamente quieren parecerse a ella
and want to buy the same clothes comment
y quieren comprar la misma ropa comenta
that you persist strategy
que te persiste estrategia
in the photo follow Pull and Bear or something
en la foto seguir a Pull and Bear o algo
else  beyond that No don't
no más allá de eso No no
believe it and in fact it's the first time
te creas y de hecho es la primera vez de
I've really felt lazy I
verdad que yo he sentido mucha pereza lo
mean it very very very very very
digo en serio mucha mucha mucha mucha
lazy very lazy to you very
mucha pereza mucha pereza a ti mucha de
truly and for that reason next year
verdad y por lo mismo el año que viene
I'm going to hell I'm not going to
yo me voy a la [__] no me voy a la
hell for not doing live but for
[__] de que no haga directo sino de
saying no to inviting me to all my
decir no me invitarme a mí a todos mis
friends that go there we'll hit each other like crazy
colegas que vamos para allá nos pegamos
but get off
un siagazo que no vea pero quitarme de
this because if I get on any social network the
esto que si me meto en alguna red social
only thing I read is garbage and I don't feel like it
lo único que Leo basura y no me apetece
is that I don't feel like it the truth then I've
es que no me apetece la verdad entonces
reached that point of saying next year
he llegado a ese punto decir el año que
passing a bit but not for nothing
viene pasando un poco pero no por nada
but because when I see that nothing
sino porque es que cuando veo que nada
else is happening then I say I
más que hay movida pues digo yo en
really am not there then I really enjoy
verdad yo no estoy luego yo disfruto
that people really
mucho de que la gente me de verdad que
value what I do of course man
valore lo que hago por supuestísimo tío
I've read many of you
yo he leído a muchos de vosotros
telling me that what Congratulations how are you
diciéndome que que Enhorabuena que tal
then many people joking around saying
luego mucha gente vacilando diciendo
brothers that I've given a second wake up
hermanos que he dado segundo espabila
that I laugh my dick off with people
que me parto la [__] con la gente
joking around with me but when I also have
vacilándome pero cuando también tengo el
Twitter full  from people who don't
Twitter lleno de gente que a mí ni me
follow me or are the least bit interested in what I
sigue ni le interesa un mínimo lo que
do telling me that I'm there No,
hago diciéndome que yo ahí No yo ahí no
I'm not there, who the [ __ ] am I, I don't know what it's not the same date but I'm saying it's that I'm lazy about this, what am I doing reading this, what am I reading this for if I'm not sitting in a daycare in first grade, man
una guardería en primero de primaria tío
reading [ __ ] little kids in a playground
leyendo a [__] niños chicos en un patio
fighting and pulling each other's hair there are
peleándose y tirándose de los pelos hay
a lot of brats I say but
una cantidad de niñatos que digo pero yo
why am I reading this if this does
porque estoy leyendo esto si a mí esto
n't contribute anything to me what am I doing because I'm crazy and I haven't
no me aporta nada qué hago por loquito y
read anything from anyone for a long time
llevo un montón sin leer nada de nadie
because the people who
porque no me aporta la gente que me
tell me nice things don't contribute anything to me of course it
decís cosas bonitas por supuesto que me
contributes to me I have the feedback and on reddit I
aporta yo tengo el feedback y en reddit
laugh my ass off beyond that I
que me parto el cipotes más allá de eso
consider it necessary to read more
Considero que no es necesario leer más
with all the people who talk to me on
con la de gente que me habla por
Instagram and everywhere but I think
Instagram y por todos lados pero yo creo
that your head has reached a point of no
que ya tu cabeza llegó un punto de no
return of saying either I stop or I
retorno de decir o paro o vivo
constantly live with what they will say and what
constantemente con el qué dirán y el Qué
people think of me that
piensa la gente de mí que me está
people are telling me about this that I have
diciendo la gente sobre esto que he
said about this  that I've done Well and
dicho sobre esto que he hecho Bueno y
because I don't have tiktok God save me
porque yo no tengo tiktok Dios me salve
from having that [ __ ] [ __ ] at the moment
de tener esa [__] [__] en el momento
in which I have to take as
en el que yo tengo que tomar como
opinions there is something else to see like that
opiniones hay algo más que ver así
based no no well you're absolutely right Juanito well you're
basado no no pues toda la razón Juanito
absolutely right Juan my soul finally a
pues toda la razón Juan mi alma por fin
great one who says things as they are
uno grande que dice las cosas como son
eh it's that you literally don't have to be
eh es que literalmente no tienes que
afraid to say these kinds of things
tener miedo a decir este tipo de cosas
man I mean you don't have to be afraid to
tío O sea no tienes que tener miedo de
say these kinds of things because [ __ ] yes
decir este tipo de cosas porque [__] sí
in the end
que al final
[Music]
[Música]